### Kevin Doh

San Jose, CA 95138

Phone: 408-960-5481 | Email: kdoh52@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kdoh/ | GitHub: https://github.com/kdoh52

Portfolio: https://kdoh52.github.io/

# Summary

Full Stack Web Developer employing a BA in UI/UX Design to build efficient, intuitive, and mobile responsive web applications. Effectively combines technical and creative skills to develop modern solutions, both visual and practical, using readable, scalable code. Experienced with writing, testing, and debugging code, as well as rapid prototyping, iterating, and wireframing. Communicates well in a fast-paced, collaborative, agile team environment.

#### Technical Skills

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, ES6 JavaScript, Express, SQL, NoSQL, Handlebars, Python

Frameworks/Libraries: Node.js, React, Redux, MongoDB, Mongoose, APIs, NPM, jQuery, AJAX, JSON,

Bootstrap, Material-UI

Concepts: Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), MVC paradigm, Authentication, JWT/Cookies

Applications: Visual Studio Code, Git/GitHub, MySQL, Adobe Creative Suite

# **Projects**

Delivery Dash | https://delivery-dash | https://delivery-dash-app.herokuapp.com/

- Responsive web application that allows users to search, order, and deliver food with others.
- Designed, developed, and deployed independently in 2 weeks. Implemented both front-end styling and back-end server routing.
- Utilized 2 third-party APIs, JWT Authentication, and remote MongoDB database with multiple models. Client-side state management using Redux.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Axios, Bcryptjs, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, JWT, Moment, React, React-Router-Dom, Redux, Redux-Thunk, Material-UI, Heroku

The Coder's Corner | https://github.com/joeschlick/the-coders-corner | https://the-coders-corner.herokuapp.com/

- Social media website geared towards helping web developers network, learn, and collaborate.
- Collaborated in a team of 4 full stack developers to design, develop, debug, and deploy the application within 4 weeks.
- Applied design and usability practices to enhance user experience.
- Implemented newsfeed and chat pages. Assisted in user authentication, back-end routing, APIs, database management, and general debugging
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Axios, Bcryptjs, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Passport, Socket.io, Validator, React, React-Router-Dom, Material-UI, Heroku

OMDB Movie Search | https://github.com/kdoh52/movie-search | https://shoppies-movie-search.herokuapp.com/

- Website that allows a user to search the OMDB API and save/remove books from the remote database. Prevents duplicate movie entries in saved movies list.
- Designed and developed independently using the React development lifecycle.
- Search bar to query the API. Use of dynamic React components to display results. MongoDB database to allow for saved movie data to persist.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, React, React-Dom, Axios, CORS, Dotenv, If-env, Concurrently, MongoDB, Mongoose, Atlas, OMDB API, Material-UI, Heroku

## Experience

Student Graphic Designer (Oct 2019 - Aug 2020)

UC Davis Global Affairs — Davis, CA

- Designed and edited graphics for 2018-2019 Annual Report to highlight and detail organization's accomplishments and statistics.
- Developed visual solutions for over 70 projects given constraints and specifications provided by project coordinators.
- Consistently balanced 5-10 unique projects simultaneously
- Collaborated with upper-level management and other designers on a regular basis.

Social Media / Design Intern (Apr 2019 - Sep 2019)

Davis Sensory Institute — Davis, CA

- Redesigned and maintained company website on a new platform to improve user experience and functionality.
- Designed book cover for company president's 400-page research publication.
- Assisted in conducting sensory research for over 100 participants.

Artistic Advisor (Oct 2018 - May 2019)

SoNE1 — Davis, CA

- Co-managed team of over 25 people.
- Collaborated with members in creatively developing choreographies.
- Designed graphics for promotional material on social media and public screen display.
- Mixed audio and edited videos for YouTube channel with over 250,000 subscribers.

#### Education

Coding Bootcamp Certificate: Full Stack Web Development University of California, Davis Jun 2020 - Dec 2020

Bachelor of Arts (BA): UI/UX Design University of California, Davis Sept 2017 - Dec 2020